http://www.seattlefoundation.org/privacy

Privacy Policies
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.
Last Updated: August 2016
This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the terms and conditions governing use of the Seattle Foundation Website ("Terms of Use"). Parts of those Terms of Use affect this Privacy Policy, so unless you have already done so, please review them prior to using Seattle Foundation's Website. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy Statement have the definitions provided in the Terms of Use.
This Privacy Policy describes the information collected from visitors to Seattle Foundation's Website. Seattle Foundation may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this posting, with the new terms taking effect on the date of posting. You can determine if any changes were made to this Privacy Policy by noting the date that the Privacy Policy was last updated. The practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Website and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered offline.
What Information is Collected About Me?
Information Seattle Foundation Collects That You Do Not Provide
Like all organizations with a website, Seattle Foundation receives standard usage and performance data from visitors to the Website; for example, through the use of "cookies" and other tracking mechanisms. This data is designed to be anonymous and does not identify who you are. Seattle Foundation collects at least the following: your domain name and host for Internet access; the Internet address of the site from which you came; the date and time of your access; your computer's IP address and information about its operating system, browser and host; the date and time you access the Site and the pages you visit. For each visitor to the Website, Seattle Foundation's servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the IP address or domain name (e.g., seattlefoundation.org) of visitors. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website. Your IP address also is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.
Information Seattle Foundation Collects That You Provide
It is always your choice, or the choice of anyone acting for you, whether to provide personal information. However, some information must be provided to participate in certain programs or activities (such as posting to the Giving Center), so your decision not to provide information might limit or eliminate certain functions of the Website or the ability to participate. The kinds of personal information Seattle Foundation requests from and about you or others varies based on the context, but may include without limitation your name, email address, organization name, job title, city, state/province, region, age. Other information you provide is up to your good judgment, e.g., do not provide personal information about yourself that could be misused by others in a chat room, bulletin board, blog or similar forum and do not provide personal information about others without their permission.
Information You Provide About Others
Do not supply personal information about others unless you are authorized or required to do so by applicable law or contract and you consent to the Terms of Use (including this Privacy Policy) on behalf of yourself and the "data subject" (the person about whom you supply personal information). Before supplying personal information about others (except as otherwise allowed by law or contract), you must make available for the data subject’s review, and obtain their written consent to our Terms of Use. By submitting any personal information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to do so and that you did all of the foregoing before submitting the information. If applicable law allows you to supply the information without doing the foregoing, you represent and warrant that you have abided by that law and that it allows us to receive and disclose the information under this Privacy Policy without any further action on our part. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold us harmless against any failure by you to comply with this paragraph.
Seattle Foundation works with third parties that own or are responsible for that program's website. In those cases, if you provide personal information, you will be giving it to a third party and its privacy policy will apply.
Seattle Foundation's Use of Information
Seattle Foundation generally does not provide any personally identifiable information to anyone regarding Seattle Foundation Website users other than information that Website users post on the Website, including interactive sections of the site such as the Community Knowledge Center, Discussion Boards and Nonprofit Profile sections. Seattle Foundation may use anonymous information gathered from the Website, which may include anonymous information gathered about you, for various purposes. Seattle Foundation only uses personal information it collects to pursue our mission and operations and uses all such data in compliance with applicable law.
Seattle Foundation’s Use of Donor Information
Seattle Foundation particularly respects and values the trust you place in us when you give us your personal information in connection with a donation. We do not sell, rent, loan, or otherwise share any personally identifying information about our donors without their permission. Seattle Foundation restricts access to donor’s personal information to those employees or contractors who need to know that personal information to provide our services to you. This policy regarding use of donor information applies to all donor information, however received, including information collected offline.
Exceptions
While Seattle Foundation strives to protect the personal information of our users and donors in every case, please note that Seattle Foundation will release your personal information (a) to service providers to verify, process, store, enforce, investigate, or assist with transactions and operations (e.g. credit card processors, auditors); (b) if required by law, government investigation, or legal process or (c) in exigent circumstances where we have the good-faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate.
Note About Children's Privacy Issues
Seattle Foundation's primary audience is adults and young adults interested in philanthropic endeavors. For that reason, when you register, Seattle Foundation will ask you to confirm that you are over the age of 13.
Seattle Foundation has no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. Any use of the Website by children under the age of 13 should only be conducted under the supervision of that child’s parent or guardian. If a child has provided his or her personal information, a parent or guardian may so inform us by emailing m.roske [at] seattlefoundation.org or calling (206) 622-2294 and Seattle Foundation will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that child’s personal information from our database (subject to applicable law and this Privacy Policy).
Seattle Foundation recommends that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.
Cookies
Seattle Foundation may place a "cookie" on the browser of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on websites and many major websites use them to provide useful features to their visitors. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, but may be used to tell when your computer has contacted our Website. You may set your browser to reject cookies, but please understand that certain features of the Website may not be available if your browser does not accept cookies. We never use or install spyware on your computer.
We also may use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any interactive portion of the Website, such as the Community Knowledge Center, Discussion Boards and Nonprofit Profile sections.
Links
Seattle Foundation’s Website contains links to other sites. Seattle Foundation is not responsible for the privacy practices, the terms and conditions of use, or any of the content of such websites. The linked sites may collect personal information from you that is not subject to Seattle Foundation's control. The data collection practices of linked sites will be governed by that site’s privacy policy, not by that of Seattle Foundation.
What Steps Are Taken to Keep Personal Information Secure?
Seattle Foundation is committed to protecting the security of your personal information in its possession. Seattle Foundation will take reasonable security precautions designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. While Seattle Foundation has mechanisms in place designed to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, we cannot guarantee that your personal information will be secure.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Seattle Foundation reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy in our discretion in accordance with the provisions in the Terms of Use regarding amendments, including changes that will retroactively apply to data that Seattle Foundation already has collected from you. If Seattle Foundation makes any substantial changes Seattle Foundation will notify you by posting a notice with the revised Privacy Policy, and through any other means, such as notices on the Website, that Seattle Foundation deems appropriate and reasonable.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or other matters that relate to it, you may contact us at:
